<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>cs-risker的博客</title><link>https://cs-risker.github.io</link><description>总结分享计算机科学的一些知识...</description><copyright>cs-risker的博客</copyright><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/206727409?v=4</url><title>avatar</title><link>https://cs-risker.github.io</link></image><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 15:44:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><managingEditor>cs-risker的博客</managingEditor><ttl>60</ttl><webMaster>cs-risker的博客</webMaster><item><title>第一篇文章测试</title><link>https://cs-risker.github.io/post/di-yi-pian-wen-zhang-ce-shi.html</link><description>test。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cs-risker.github.io/post/di-yi-pian-wen-zhang-ce-shi.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 07:27:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://cs-risker.github.io/about.html</link><description># Educational Experience
* Central South University; School of Computer Science; Computer Science and Technology
* Huazhong University of Science and Technology; Wuhan National Laboratory for Optoelectronics/School of Computer Science and Technology; Computer Technology 
# Technology Footprints
## 1.Data Structures and Algorithms
I'm familiar with commonly used data structure and algorithm programming ideas, and have recorded the solutions of various classic problems on leetcode, uploading them to my github: [leetcode-notes]()
## 2.Computer Architecture
I have studied the classic textbook 'Computer Systems: A Programmer's Perspective' from Carnegie Mellon University, also known as 'CSAPP'. During this process, I took detailed notes on most of the chapters, and these notes can be searched on the blog of my homepage(please search for: CSAPP Reading Notes).
## 3.Other Useful Tools
In addition to the important computer professional knowledge mentioned above, I have also explored a certain range of common tools in the field of computers, and I have discussions on most of them in my blog(for example,you can search for:  GitHub remote branch management). Below, I have listed a portion of them：
* CMake
* gdb
* git
* shell
* ......
# Project Experience
## 1.CMU15-213:CSAPP
### description
This project is from the course experiment of cmu-15213. During the process, I recorded detailed experimental procedures, which can all be found on my blog (please search for: cmu15-213 experiment records on the homepage). In addition, all the source code for the experiment has been uploaded to my GitHub:[cmu15213-lab]()
### technology stack
* Mainly Involving knowledge：Computer Architecture
* Mainly Involving technology：C language; gdb; shell
### main content
* Data Lab：The experiment requires learners to implement various data processing functions, such as logical operations, arithmetic operations, and data conversions, using a limited set of operational instructions within a strictly restricted programming environment, thereby gaining a deep understanding of the underlying principles of bit manipulation in computers.
* Bomb Lab：The experiment requires learners to use debugging tools (such as GDB) and disassembly tools (such as objdump) to analyze and debug binary code, which helps to enhance the understanding of machine-level code, program execution processes, stack frame structures, and other related knowledge.
# Personal Interests
Badminton; movies; certain games
# Contact Me
* CSDN：
* Github：
* E-Mail：。</description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cs-risker.github.io/about.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 14:49:37 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>